{
  "isTheory": true,
  "openingRemarks": "Find the solution to the following equations",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(3w + 7 = 19 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3w + 7 &= 19 \\\\\n3w &= 19 - 7 \\\\\n3w &= 12 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3w}{3} &= \\dfrac{12}{3} \\\\\nw &= 4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 19 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(3w + 7\\) if \\(w=4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 3(4) + 7 \\\\\n&= 12 + 7 \\\\\n&= 19\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2g - 13 = 3 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2g - 13 &= 3 \\\\\n2g &= 3 + 13 \\\\\n2g &= 16 \\\\\n\\dfrac{2g}{2} &= \\dfrac{16}{2} \\\\\ng &= 8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 3 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2g - 13\\) if \\(g=8\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 2(8) - 13 \\\\\n&= 16 - 13 \\\\\n&= 3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(11 = 12 - q \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n11 &= 12 - q \\\\\n11 - 12 &= -q \\\\\n-1 &= -q \\\\\n\\dfrac{-1}{-1} &= \\dfrac{-q}{-1} \\\\\n1 &= q \\\\\nq &= 1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 11 = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(12 - q\\) if \\(q=1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 12 - 1 \\\\\n&= 11\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(10 = 7 - m \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10 &= 7 - m \\\\\n10 - 7 &= -m \\\\\n3 &= -m\\\\\n\\dfrac{3}{-1} &= \\dfrac{-m}{-1} \\\\\n-3 &= m \\\\\nm &= -3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 10 = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(7 - m\\) if \\(m=-3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 7 - (-3) \\\\\n&= 7 + 3 \\\\\n&= 10\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 = \\dfrac{z}{-4} - 3 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5 &= \\dfrac{z}{-4} - 3 \\\\\n-4 \\times 5 &= -4 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{z}{-4} - 3\\right) \\\\\n-20 &= z + 12 \\\\\n-20 - 12 &= z \\\\\n-32 &= z \\\\\nz &= -32\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 5 = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{z}{-4} - 3\\) if \\(z=-32\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{-32}{-4} -3 \\\\\n&= 8 - 3 \\\\\n&= 5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{a}{3} + 4 = 6 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{a}{3} + 4 &= 6 \\\\\n3 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{a}{3} + 4\\right) &= 3 \\times 6 \\\\\n3\\left(\\dfrac{a}{3}\\right) + 3 \\times 4 &= 18 \\\\\na + 12 &= 18 \\\\\na &= 18 - 12 \\\\\na &= 6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 6 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{a}{3} + 4\\) if \\(a=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{6}{3} + 4 \\\\\n&= 2 + 4 \\\\\n&= 6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{h + 6}{5} = 2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{h + 6}{5} &= 2 \\\\\n5 \\times \\dfrac{h+6}{5} &= 5 \\times 2 \\\\\nh + 6 &= 10 \\\\\nh &= 10 - 6 \\\\\nh &= 4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 2 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{h+6}{5}\\) if \\(h=4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{4+6}{5} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{10}{5} \\\\\n&= 2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{d - 8}{-2} = 12 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{d - 8}{-2} &= 12 \\\\\n-2 \\times \\dfrac{d-8}{-2} &= -2 \\times 12 \\\\\nd - 8 &= -24 \\\\\nd &= -24 + 8 \\\\\nd &= -16\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 12 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{d-8}{-2}\\) if \\(d=-16\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{-16-8}{-2} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{-24}{-2} \\\\\n&= 12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8y + 3y = 44 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8y + 3y &= 44 \\\\\n11y &= 44 \\\\\n\\dfrac{11y}{11} &= \\dfrac{44}{11} \\\\\ny &= 4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 44</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(8y + 3y\\) if \\(y=4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 8(4) + 3(4) \\\\\n&= 32 + 12 \\\\\n&= 44\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(36 = 13n - 4n \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n36 &= 13n - 4n \\\\\n36 &= 9n \\\\\n\\dfrac{36}{9} &= \\dfrac{9n}{9} \\\\\n4 &= n \\\\\nn &= 4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 36 = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(13n - 4n\\) if \\(n=4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 13(4) - 4(4) \\\\\n&= 52 - 16 \\\\\n&= 36 \n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(12y + 10y + 14 = 80 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n12y + 10y + 14 &= 80 \\\\\n22y + 14 &= 80 \\\\\n22y &= 80 - 14 \\\\\n22y &= 66 \\\\\n\\dfrac{22y}{22} &= \\dfrac{66}{22} \\\\\ny &= 3 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 80</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(12y + 10y + 14\\) if \\(y=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 12(3) + 10(3) + 14 \\\\\n&= 36 + 30 + 14 \\\\\n&= 80\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6c - 8 - 2c = -16 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6c - 8 - 2c &= -16 \\\\\n6c - 2c &= -16 + 8 \\\\\n4c &= -8 \\\\\n\\dfrac{4c}{4} &= \\dfrac{-8}{4} \\\\\nc &= -2 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -16</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(6c - 8 - 2c\\) if \\(c=-2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 6(-2) - 8 - 2(-2) \\\\\n&= -12 - 8 - -4 \\\\\n&= -12 - 8 + 4 \\\\\n&= -16\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4(z + 5) = 32 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4(z + 5) &= 32 \\\\\n4z + 20 &= 32 \\\\\n4z &= 32 - 20 \\\\\n4z &= 12 \\\\\n\\dfrac{4z}{4} &= \\dfrac{12}{4} \\\\\nz &= 3 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 32</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4(z + 5)\\) if \\(z=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 4(3 + 5) \\\\\n&= 4(8) \\\\\n&= 32\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-2(4g - 3) = 30 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-2(4g - 3) &= 30 \\\\\n-8g + 6 &= 30 \\\\\n-8g &= 30 - 6 \\\\\n-8g &= 24 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-8g}{-8} &= \\dfrac{24}{-8} \\\\\ng &= -3 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 30</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-2(4g - 3)\\) if \\(g=-3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -2(4(-3) - 3) \\\\\n&= -2(-12 - 3) \\\\\n&= -2(-15) \\\\\n&= 30\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 + 5(m + 1) = 26 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6 + 5(m + 1) &= 26 \\\\\n6 +5m + 5 &= 26 \\\\\n5m &= 26 - 6 - 5 \\\\\n5m &= 15 \\\\\n\\dfrac{5m}{5} &= \\dfrac{15}{5} \\\\\nm &= 3 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 26</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(6+5(m + 1)\\) if \\(m=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 6 + 5(3 + 1) \\\\\n&= 6 + 5(4) \\\\\n&= 6 + 20 \\\\\n&= 26\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5h + 2(11 - h) = -5 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5h + 2(11 - h) &= -5 \\\\\n5h +22 - 2h &= -5 \\\\\n5h - 2h &=  -5 - 22 \\\\\n3h &= -27 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3h}{3} &= \\dfrac{-27}{3} \\\\\nh &= -9 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -5</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5h+2(11 - h)\\) if \\(h=-9\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 5(-9) + 2(11 - (-9)) \\\\\n&= -45 + 2(11 + 9) \\\\\n&= -45 + 2(20) \\\\\n&= -45 + 40 \\\\\n&= -5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(27 = 3c - 3(6 - 2c) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n27 &= 3c - 3(6 - 2c) \\\\\n27 &= 3c - 18 + 6c \\\\\n27 + 18 &=  3c + 6c \\\\\n45 &= 9c \\\\\n\\dfrac{45}{9} &= \\dfrac{9c}{9} \\\\\n5 &= c \\\\\nc &= 5 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 27= RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(3c-3(6 - 2c)\\) if \\(c=5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 3(5) - 3(6 - 2(5)) \\\\\n&= 15 - 3(6 - 10) \\\\\n&= 15 - 3(-4) \\\\\n&= 15 + 12 \\\\\n&= 27\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-3 = 12y - 5(2y - 7) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-3 &= 12y - 5(2y - 7) \\\\\n-3 &= 12y - 10y + 35 \\\\\n-3  &=  2y + 35 \\\\\n-2y &= 35 + 3 \\\\\n-2y &= 38 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-2y}{-2} &= \\dfrac{38}{-2} \\\\\ny &= -19 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check -3 = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(12y-5(2y - 7)\\) if \\(y=-19\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 12(-19) - 5(2(-19) - 7) \\\\\n&= -228 - 5(-38 - 7) \\\\\n&= -228 - 5(-45) \\\\\n&= -228 + 225 \\\\\n&= -3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-3(3 + x) + 4(x - 6) = -4 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-3(3 + x) + 4(x - 6) &= -4 \\\\\n-9 - 3x + 4x - 24 &= -4 \\\\\n-3x + 4x  &=  -4 + 9 + 24 \\\\\nx &= 29 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -4</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-3(3 + x) + 4(x - 6)\\) if \\(x=29\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -3(3 + 29) + 4(29 - 6) \\\\\n&= -3(32) + 4(23) \\\\\n&= -96 + 92 \\\\\n&= -4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5(r + 9) - 2(1 - r) = 1 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5(r + 9) - 2(1 - r) &= 1 \\\\\n5r + 45 - 2 + 2r &= 1 \\\\\n5r + 2r  &=  1 - 45 +2 \\\\\n7r &= -42 \\\\\n\\dfrac{7r}{7} &= \\dfrac{-42}{7} \\\\\nr &= -6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 1</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5(r + 9) - 2(1 - r)\\) if \\(r=-6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 5(-6 + 9) - 2(1 - (-6)) \\\\\n&= 5(3) - 2(1 + 6) \\\\\n&= 15 - 2(7) \\\\\n&= 15 - 14 \\\\\n&= 1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(15 - 2x = 3x \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n15 - 2x &= 3x \\\\\n15 &= 3x + 2x \\\\\n15  &=  5x \\\\\n\\dfrac{15}{5} &= \\dfrac{5x}{5} \\\\\n3 &= x \\\\\nx &= 3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(15 - 2x\\) if \\(x=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 15 - 2(3) \\\\\n&= 15 - 6 \\\\\n&= 9\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(3x\\) if \\(x=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 3(3) \\\\\n&= 9\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(26 - 4s = 9s \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n26 - 4s &= 9s \\\\\n26 &= 9s + 4s \\\\\n26 &=  13s \\\\\n\\dfrac{26}{13} &= \\dfrac{13s}{13} \\\\\n2 &= s \\\\\ns &= 2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(26 - 4s\\) if \\(s=2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 26 - 4(2) \\\\\n&= 26 - 8 \\\\\n&= 18\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(9s\\) if \\(s=2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 9(2) \\\\\n&= 18\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5p - 9 = 2p + 12 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5p - 9 &= 2p + 12 \\\\\n5p - 2p &= 12 + 9 \\\\\n3p &=  21 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3p}{3} &= \\dfrac{21}{3} \\\\\np &= 7 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5p - 9\\) if \\(p=7\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 5(7) - 9 \\\\\n&= 35 - 9 \\\\\n&= 26\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2p + 12\\) if \\(p=7\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 2(7) + 12 \\\\\n&= 14 + 12 \\\\\n&= 26\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8g + 10 = 35 + 3g \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8g + 10 &= 35 + 3g \\\\\n8g - 3g &= 35 - 10 \\\\\n5g &=  25 \\\\\n\\dfrac{5g}{5} &= \\dfrac{25}{5} \\\\\ng &= 5 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(8g + 10\\) if \\(g=5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 8(5) + 10 \\\\\n&= 40 + 10 \\\\\n&= 50\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(35 + 3g\\) if \\(g=5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 35 + 3(5) \\\\\n&= 35 + 15 \\\\\n&= 50\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5t + 16 = 6 - 5t \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5t + 16 &= 6 - 5t \\\\\n5t + 5t &= 6 - 16 \\\\\n10t &=  -10 \\\\\n\\dfrac{10t}{10} &= \\dfrac{-10}{10} \\\\\nt &= -1 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5t + 16\\) if \\(t=-1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 5(-1) + 16 \\\\\n&= -5 + 16 \\\\\n&= 11\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(6 - 5t\\) if \\(t=-1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 6 - 5(-1) \\\\\n&= 6 + 5 \\\\\n&= 11\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-3r + 10 = 15r - 8 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-3r + 10 &= 15r - 8 \\\\\n-3r - 15r &= -8 - 10 \\\\\n-18r &=  -18 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-18r}{-18} &= \\dfrac{-18}{-18} \\\\\nr &= 1 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-3r + 10\\) if \\(r=1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -3(1) + 10 \\\\\n&= -3 + 10 \\\\\n&= 7\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(15r - 8\\) if \\(r=1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 15(1) - 8 \\\\\n&= 15 - 8 \\\\\n&= 7\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 + 3x - 12x = 3x + 1 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n7 + 3x - 12x &= 3x + 1 \\\\\n7 - 1 &= 3x + 12x -3x \\\\\n6 &= 12x \\\\\n\\dfrac{6}{12} &= \\dfrac{12x}{12} \\\\\n\\frac{1}{2} &= x \\\\\nx &= \\frac{1}{2} \\text{ or } x = 0.5 \n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(7 + 3x  -  12x\\) if \\(x=\\frac{1}{2}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 7 + 3\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right) -  12\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right) \\\\\n&= 7 + \\dfrac{3}{2} - 6 \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{5}{2}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(3x + 1\\) if \\(x=\\frac{1}{2}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 3\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right) + 1 \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{3}{2} + 1  \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{5}{2}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(w - 2 + 2w = 6 + 5w \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nw - 2 + 2w &= 6 + 5w \\\\\nw + 2w - 5w  &= 6 + 2 \\\\\n-2w &= 8 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-2w}{-2} &= \\dfrac{8}{-2} \\\\\nw &= -4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(w - 2  +  2w\\) if \\(w=-4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -4 - 2 + 2(-4) \\\\\n&= -6 + (-8) \\\\\n&= -14\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(6 + 5w\\) if \\(w=-4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 6 + 5(-4) \\\\\n&= 6 - 20  \\\\\n&= -14\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(10(g + 5) = 2(g + 9) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10(g + 5) &= 2(g + 9) \\\\\n10g + 50  &= 2g + 18 \\\\\n10g - 2g &= 18 - 50 \\\\\n8g &= -32 \\\\\n\\dfrac{8g}{8} &= \\dfrac{-32}{8} \\\\\ng &= -4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(10(g  +  5)\\) if \\(g=-4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 10(-4 + 5) \\\\\n&= 10(1) \\\\\n&= 10\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(g + 9)\\) if \\(g=-4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 2(-4 + 9) \\\\\n&= 2(5)  \\\\\n&= 10\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-9(t - 2) = 4(t - 15) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-9(t - 2) &= 4(t - 15) \\\\\n-9t + 18  &= 4t - 60 \\\\\n-9t - 4t &=  -60 - 18 \\\\\n-13t &= -78 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-13t}{-13} &= \\dfrac{-78}{-13} \\\\\nt &= 6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-9(t  - 2)\\) if \\(t=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -9(6 - 2) \\\\\n&= -9(4) \\\\\n&= -36\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4(t - 15)\\) if \\(t=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 4(6 - 15) \\\\\n&= 4(-9)  \\\\\n&= -36\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{3}(3x + 9) = -2(2x + 6) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{2}{3}(3x + 9) &= -2(2x + 6) \\\\\n3 \\times \\dfrac{2}{3}(3x + 9)  &= 3 \\times -2(2x + 6) \\\\\n2(3x + 9) &=  -6(2x + 6) \\\\\n6x + 18 &= -12x - 36 \\\\\n6x + 12x &= -36 -18 \\\\\n18x &= -54 \\\\\n\\dfrac{18x}{18} &= \\dfrac{-54}{18} \\\\\nx &= -3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{2}{3}(3x + 9)\\) if \\(x=-3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{2}{3}(3(-3) + 9) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{2}{3}(-9 + 9) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{2}{3}(0) \\\\\n&= 0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-2(2x + 6)\\) if \\(x=-3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -2(2(-3) + 6) \\\\\n&= -2(-6 + 6)  \\\\\n&= -2(0) \\\\\n&= 0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2(2t + 4) = \\dfrac{3}{4}(24 - 8t)  \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(2t + 4) &= \\dfrac{3}{4}(24 - 8t)  \\\\\n4 \\times 2(2t + 4) &= 4 \\times \\dfrac{3}{4}(24 - 8t)  \\\\\n8(2t + 4) &=  3(24 - 8t) \\\\\n16t + 32 &= 72 - 24t \\\\\n16t + 24t &= 72 - 32 \\\\\n40t &= 40 \\\\\n\\dfrac{40t}{40} &= \\dfrac{40}{40} \\\\\nt &= 1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(2t + 4)\\) if \\(t=1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 2(2(1) + 4) \\\\\n&= 2(2 + 4) \\\\\n&= 2(6) \\\\\n&= 12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{3}{4}(24 - 8t)\\) if \\(t=1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{3}{4}(24 - 8(1)) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{3}{4}(24 - 8)  \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{3}{4}(16) \\\\\n&= 12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(10(2y + 2) - y = 2(8y - 8)  \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10(2y + 2) - y &= 2(8y - 8)  \\\\\n20y + 20 - y &= 16y - 16 \\\\\n20y - y - 16y &= -16 - 20 \\\\\n3y &= -36 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3y}{3} &= \\dfrac{-36}{3} \\\\\ny &= -12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(10(2y + 2) - y\\) if \\(y=-12\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 10(2(-12) + 2) - (-12) \\\\\n&= 10(-24 + 2) + 12 \\\\\n&= 10(-22) + 12 \\\\\n&= -220 + 12\\\\\n&= -208\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(8y - 8)\\) if \\(y=-12\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 2(8(-12) - 8) \\\\\n&= 2(-96 - 8)  \\\\\n&= 2(-104) \\\\\n&= -208\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2(4x + 2) = 4x - 12(x - 1)  \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(4x + 2) &= 4x - 12(x - 1)  \\\\\n8x + 4 &= 4x - 12x + 12 \\\\\n8x - 4x + 12x &= 12 - 4 \\\\\n16x &= 8 \\\\\n\\dfrac{16x}{16} &= \\dfrac{8}{16} \\\\\nx &= \\frac{1}{2}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(4x + 2)\\) if \\(x=\\frac{1}{2}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 2\\left(4\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right) + 2\\right) \\\\\n&= 2(2 + 2) \\\\\n&= 2(4) \\\\\n&= 8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4x - 12(x - 1)\\) if \\(x=\\frac{1}{2}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 4\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right) - 12\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2} - 1\\right) \\\\\n&= 2 - 12\\left(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right)  \\\\\n&= 2 - -6 \\\\\n&= 2 + 6 \\\\\n&= 8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(x+ 9 = 7 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nx+ 9 &= 7 \\\\\nx &= 7 - 9 \\\\\nx &= -2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 7</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(x + 9\\) if \\(x=-2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -2 + 9 \\\\\n&= 7 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8.6 = z - 3.8 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8.6 &= z - 3.8 \\\\\n8.6 + 3.8 &= z \\\\\n12.4 &= z \\\\\nz &= 12.4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 8.6 = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(z - 3.8\\) if \\(z=12.4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 12.4 - 3.8 \\\\\n&= 8.6 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(60 = -12r \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n60 &= -12r \\\\\n\\dfrac{60}{-12} &= \\dfrac{-12r}{-12} \\\\\n-5 &= r \\\\\nr &= -5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 60 = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-12r\\) if \\(r=-5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -12(-5) \\\\\n&= 60 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{4}p = 18 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{3}{4}p &= 18 \\\\\n4 \\times \\dfrac{3}{4}p &= 4 \\times 18 \\\\\n3p &= 72 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3p}{3} &= \\dfrac{72}{3} \\\\\np &= 24\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 18</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{3}{4}p\\) if \\(p=24\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{3}{4}(24) \\\\\n&= 18 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2m - 3 = 13 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2m - 3 &= 13 \\\\\n2m &= 13 + 3 \\\\\n2m &= 16 \\\\\n\\dfrac{2m}{2} &= \\dfrac{16}{2} \\\\\nm &= 8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 13</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2m - 3\\) if \\(m=8\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 2(8) - 3 \\\\\n&= 16 - 3 \\\\\n&= 13\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 = 10 - v \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5 &= 10 - v \\\\\nv &= 10 - 5 \\\\\nv &= 5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 5 = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(10 - v\\) if \\(v=5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 10 - 5 \\\\\n&= 5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 = 7w + 8w + 2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5 &= 7w + 8w + 2 \\\\\n5 - 2 &= 7w + 8w \\\\\n3 &= 15w \\\\\n\\dfrac{3}{15} &= \\dfrac{15w}{15} \\\\\n\\dfrac{1}{5} &= w \\\\\nw &= \\dfrac{1}{5}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 5 = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(7w + 8w + 2\\) if \\(w=\\frac{1}{5}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 7\\left(\\dfrac{1}{5}\\right) + 8\\left(\\dfrac{1}{5}\\right) + 2 \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{7}{5} + \\dfrac{8}{5} + 2 \\\\\n&= 1.4 + 1.6 + 2 \\\\\n&= 5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-21a + 28a - 6 = -10.2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-21a + 28a - 6 &= -10.2 \\\\\n-21a + 28a &= -10.2 + 6 \\\\\n7a &= -4.2 \\\\\n\\dfrac{7a}{7} &= \\dfrac{-4.2}{7} \\\\\na &= -0.6 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -10.2</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-21a + 28a - 6\\) if \\(a=-0.6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -21(-0.6) + 28(-0.6) - 6 \\\\\n&= 12.6 - 16.8 - 6 \\\\\n&= -10.2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2k - 3(2k - 3) = 45 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2k - 3(2k - 3) &= 45 \\\\\n2k - 6k + 9 &= 45 \\\\\n-4k &= 45 - 9 \\\\\n-4k &= 36 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-4k}{-4} &= \\dfrac{36}{-4} \\\\\nk &= -9 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 45</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2k - 3(2k - 3)\\) if \\(k=-9\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 2(-9) - 3(2(-9) - 3) \\\\\n&= -18 - 3(-18 - 3) \\\\\n&= -18 - 3(-21) \\\\\n&= -18 + 63 \\\\\n&= 45\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(68 = \\dfrac{1}{5}(20x + 50) + 2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n68 &= \\dfrac{1}{5}(20x + 50) + 2 \\\\\n5 \\times 68 &= 5 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{1}{5}(20x + 50) + 2\\right) \\\\\n340 &= 5 \\times \\dfrac{1}{5}(20x + 50) + 5 \\times 2 \\\\\n340 &= 20x + 50 + 10 \\\\\n340 &= 20x + 60 \\\\\n340 - 50 - 10 &= 20x \\\\\n280 &= 20x \\\\\n\\dfrac{280}{20} &= \\dfrac{20x}{20} \\\\\n14 &= x \\\\\nx &= 14 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 68 = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{1}{5}(20x + 50) + 2\\) if \\(x=14\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{1}{5}(20(14) + 50) + 2 \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{1}{5}(280 + 50) + 2 \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{1}{5}(330) + 2 \\\\\n&= 66 + 2 \\\\\n&= 68\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3c + 1 = c + 1 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3c + 1 &= c + 1 \\\\\n3c - c &= 1 - 1 \\\\\n2c &= 0 \\\\\n\\dfrac{2c}{2} &= \\dfrac{0}{2} \\\\\nc &= 0 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(3c + 1\\) if \\(c=0\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 3(0) + 1 \\\\\n&= 0 + 1 \\\\\n&= 0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(c + 1\\) if \\(c=0\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 0 + 1 \\\\\n&= 0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-8 - 5n = 64 + 3n \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-8 - 5n &= 64 + 3n \\\\\n-5n - 3n &= 64 + 8 \\\\\n-8n &= 72 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-8n}{-8} &= \\dfrac{72}{-8} \\\\\nn &= -9 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-8 - 5n\\) if \\(n=-9\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -8 - 5(-9) \\\\\n&= -8 + 45 \\\\\n&= 37\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(64 + 3n\\) if \\(n=-9\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 64 + 3(-9) \\\\\n&= 64 - 27 \\\\\n&= 37\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2(8q - 5) = 4q \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(8q - 5) &= 4q \\\\\n16q - 10 &= 4q \\\\\n16q - 4q &= 10 \\\\\n12q &= 10 \\\\\n\\dfrac{12q}{12} &= \\dfrac{10}{12} \\\\\nq &= \\dfrac{5}{6} \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(8q - 5)\\) if \\(q=\\frac{5}{6}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 2\\left(8\\left(\\dfrac{5}{6}\\right) - 5\\right) \\\\\n&= 2\\left(\\dfrac{40}{6} - 5\\right) \\\\\n&= 2\\left(\\dfrac{5}{3}\\right) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{10}{3}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4q\\) if \\(q=\\frac{5}{6}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 4\\left(\\dfrac{5}{6}\\right) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{10}{3}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9(y - 4) - 7y = 5(3y - 2) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n9(y - 4) - 7y &= 5(3y - 2) \\\\\n9y - 36 - 7y &= 15y - 10 \\\\\n9y - 7y - 15y  &= -10 + 36 \\\\\n-13y &= 26 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-13y}{-13} &= \\dfrac{26}{-13} \\\\\ny &= -2 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(9(y - 4) - 7y\\) if \\(y=-2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 9(-2 - 4) - 7(-2) \\\\\n&= 9(-6) + 14 \\\\\n&= -54 + 14 \\\\\n&= -40\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5(3y - 2)\\) if \\(y=-2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 5(3(-2) - 2) \\\\\n&= 5(-6 - 2) \\\\\n&= 5(-8) \\\\\n&= -40\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4(g + 8) = 7 + 4g \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4(g + 8) &= 7 + 4g \\\\\n4g + 32 &= 7 + 4g  \\\\\n32- 7  &= 4g - 4g  \\\\\n25 &= 0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Since \\(25 = 0\\) is always false,  the equation does not have a solution.</div>\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-4(-5h - 4) = 2(10h + 8) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-4(-5h - 4) &= 2(10h + 8) \\\\\n20h + 16 &= 20h + 16  \\\\\n20h- 20h  &= 16 - 16  \\\\\n0 &= 0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Since \\(0=0\\) is always true, all numbers satisfy the equation.</div>\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6d + 8 = 14 + 3d \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6d + 8 &= 14 + 3d \\\\\n6d - 3d &= 14 - 8  \\\\\n3d  &= 6  \\\\\n\\dfrac{3d}{3} &= \\dfrac{6}{3} \\\\\nd &= 2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(6d + 8\\) if \\(d=2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 6(2) + 8 \\\\\n&= 12 + 8  \\\\\n&= 20\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(14 + 3d\\) if \\(d=2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 14 + 3(2) \\\\\n&= 14 + 6  \\\\\n&= 20\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2(h + 1) = 5h - 7 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(h + 1) &= 5h - 7 \\\\\n2h + 2 &= 5h - 7  \\\\\n2 + 7  &= 5h - 2h  \\\\\n9 &= 3h \\\\\n\\dfrac{9}{3} &= \\dfrac{3h}{3} \\\\\n3 &= h \\\\\nh &= 3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(h + 1)\\) if \\(h=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 2(3 + 1) \\\\\n &=  2(4)  \\\\\n&= 8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5h - 7\\) if \\(h=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 5(3) - 7 \\\\\n &= 15 - 7  \\\\\n&= 8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(n - 12 = 32 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nn - 12 &= 32 \\\\\nn &= 32 + 12  \\\\\nn &= 44 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 32</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(n - 12\\) if \\(n=44\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 44 - 12 \\\\\n&= 32\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(y + 16 = -9 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\ny + 16 &= -9 \\\\\ny &= -9 - 16  \\\\\ny &= -25 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -9</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(y + 16\\) if \\(y=-25\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -25 + 16 \\\\\n&= -9\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(f + \\dfrac{2}{3} = 4 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nf + \\dfrac{2}{3} &= 4 \\\\\n3 \\times \\left(f + \\dfrac{2}{3} \\right) &= 3 \\times 4 \\\\\n3 \\times f + 3 \\times \\dfrac{2}{3} &= 12 \\\\\n3f + 2 &= 12 \\\\\n3f &= 12 - 2 \\\\\n3f &= 10 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3f}{3} &= \\dfrac{10}{3} \\\\\nf &= \\dfrac{10}{3}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 4</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(f + \\dfrac{2}{3}\\) if \\(f=\\frac{10}{3}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{10}{3} + \\dfrac{2}{3} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{12}{3} \\\\\n&= 4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(d - 3.9 = 8.2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nd - 3.9 &= 8.2 \\\\\nd &= 8.2 + 3.9 \\\\\nd &= 12.1 \n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 8.2</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(d - 3.9\\) if \\(d=12.1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 12.1 - 3.9 \\\\\n&= 8.2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7x + 10 - 6x + 3 = 5 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n7x + 10 - 6x + 3 &= 5 \\\\\n7x - 6x &= 5 - 10 - 3 \\\\\nx &= -8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 5</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(7x + 10 - 6x + 3\\) if \\(x=-8\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 7(-8) + 10 - 6(-8) + 3 \\\\\n&= -56 + 10 + 48 + 3 \\\\\n&= 5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6(n - 1) - 5n = -14 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6(n - 1) - 5n &= -14 \\\\\n6n - 6 - 5n &= -14 \\\\\n6n - 5n &= -14 + 6 \\\\\nn &= -8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -14</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(6(n - 1) - 5n\\) if \\(n=-8\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 6(-8 - 1) - 5(-8) \\\\\n&= 6(-9) + 40 \\\\\n&= -54 + 40 \\\\\n&= -14\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8(3p + 5) - 23(p - 1) = 35 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8(3p + 5) - 23(p - 1) &= 35 \\\\\n24p + 40 - 23p + 23  &= 35 \\\\\n24p - 23p &= 35 - 40 - 23 \\\\\np &= -28\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 35</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(8(3p + 5) - 23(p - 1)\\) if \\(p=-28\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 8(3(-28) + 5) - 23(-28 - 1) \\\\\n&= 8(-84 + 5) - 23(-29) \\\\\n&= 8(-79) + 667 \\\\\n&= -632 + 667 \\\\\n&= 35\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-18m = -72 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-18m &= -72 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-18m}{-18} &= \\dfrac{-72}{-18} \\\\\nm &= 4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -72</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-18m\\) if \\(m=4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -18(4) \\\\\n&= 72\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.45x = 6.75 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.45x &= 6.75 \\\\\n\\dfrac{0.45x}{0.45} &= \\dfrac{6.75}{0.45} \\\\\nx &= 15\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 6.75</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.45x\\) if \\(x=15\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 0.45(15) \\\\\n&= 6.75\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{c}{9} = 36 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{c}{9} &= 36 \\\\\n9 \\times \\dfrac{c}{9} &= 9 \\times 36 \\\\\nc &= 324\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 36</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{c}{9}\\) if \\(c=324\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{324}{9} \\\\\n&= 36\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{12} = \\dfrac{2}{3}y \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{11}{12} &= \\dfrac{2}{3}y \\\\\n12 \\times \\dfrac{11}{12} &= 12 \\times \\dfrac{2}{3}y \\\\\n11 &= 4(2y) \\\\\n11 &= 8y \\\\\n\\dfrac{11}{8} &= \\dfrac{8y}{8} \\\\\n\\dfrac{11}{8} &= y \\\\\ny &= \\dfrac{11}{8}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check \\(\\dfrac{11}{12}\\) = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{2}{3}y\\) if \\(y=\\dfrac{11}{8}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{2}{3} \\times \\dfrac{11}{8} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{22}{24} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{11}{12}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5r - 3r + 9r = 35 - 2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5r - 3r + 9r &= 35 - 2 \\\\\n2r + 9r &= 33 \\\\\n11r &= 33 \\\\\n\\dfrac{11r}{11} &= \\dfrac{33}{11} \\\\\nr &= 3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 33</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5r - 3r + 9r\\) if \\(r=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 5(3) - 3(3) + 9(3) \\\\\n&= 15 - 9 + 27 \\\\\n&= 33\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(y + 8 - 15 = -3 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\ny + 8 - 15 &= -3 \\\\\ny &= -3 + 15 - 8 \\\\\ny &= 4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -3</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(y + 8 - 15\\) if \\(y=4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 4 + 8 - 15 \\\\\n&= -3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(24x + 8x - 11x = -7 - 14 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n24x + 8x - 11x &= -7 - 14 \\\\\n21x &= -21 \\\\\n\\dfrac{21x}{21} &= \\dfrac{-21}{21} \\\\\nx &= -1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -21</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(24x + 8x - 11x\\) if \\(x=-1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 24(-1) + 8(-1) - 11(-1) \\\\\n&= -24 - 8 + 11 \\\\\n&= -21\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8p + 7 = 47 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8p + 7 &= 47 \\\\\n8p &= 47 - 7 \\\\\n\\dfrac{8p}{8} &= \\dfrac{40}{8} \\\\\np &= 5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 47</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(8p + 7\\) if \\(p=5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 8(5) + 7 \\\\\n&= 40+ 7 \\\\\n&= 47\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(10w - 5 = 65 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10w - 5 &= 65 \\\\\n10w &= 65 + 5 \\\\\n10w &= 70 \\\\\n\\dfrac{10w}{10} &= \\dfrac{70}{10} \\\\\nw &= 7\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 65</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(10w - 5\\) if \\(w=7\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 10(7) - 5 \\\\\n&= 70 - 5 \\\\\n&= 65\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3x + 19 = -47 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3x + 19 &= -47 \\\\\n3x &= -47 - 19 \\\\\n3x &= -66 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3x}{3} &= \\dfrac{-66}{3} \\\\\nx &= -22\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -47</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(3x + 19\\) if \\(x=-47\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 3(-22) + 19 \\\\\n&= -66 + 19 \\\\\n&= -47\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(32 = -4 - 9n \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n32 &= -4 - 9n \\\\\n32 + 4 &= -9n \\\\\n36 &= -9n \\\\\n\\dfrac{36}{-9} &= \\dfrac{-9n}{-9} \\\\\n-4 &= n\\\\\nn &= -4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 32 = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-4 - 9n\\) if \\(n=-4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -4 - 9(-4) \\\\\n&= -4 + 36 \\\\\n&= 32\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7y = 6y - 13 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n7y &= 6y - 13 \\\\\n7y - 6y &= -13 \\\\\ny &= -13\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(7y\\) if \\(y=-13\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 7(-13) \\\\\n&= -91\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(6y - 13\\) if \\(y=-13\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 6(-13) - 13 \\\\\n&= -78 - 13 \\\\\n&= -91\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5a + 21 = 2a \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5a + 21 &= 2a \\\\\n5a - 2a &= -21 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3a}{3} &= \\dfrac{-21}{3} \\\\\na &= -7\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5a + 21\\) if \\(a=-7\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 5(-7) + 21 \\\\\n&= -35 + 21 \\\\\n&= -14\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2a\\) if \\(a=-7\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 2(-7) \\\\\n&= -14\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(k = -6k  - 35\\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nk &= -6k  - 35\\\\\nk + 6k &= -35 \\\\\n7k &= -35 \\\\\n\\dfrac{7k}{7} &= \\dfrac{-35}{7} \\\\\nk &= -5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(k\\) if \\(k=-5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-6k - 35\\) if \\(k=-5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 6(-5) - 35 \\\\\n&= 30 - 35 \\\\\n&= -5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4x - \\dfrac{3}{8} = 3x \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4x - \\dfrac{3}{8} &= 3x \\\\\n8 \\times \\left(4x - \\dfrac{3}{8}\\right) &= 8 \\times 3x \\\\\n8 \\times 4x - 8 \\times \\dfrac{3}{8} &= 24x \\\\\n32x - 3 &= 24x \\\\\n32x - 24x &= 3 \\\\\n8x &= 3 \\\\\n\\dfrac{8x}{8} &= \\dfrac{3}{8} \\\\\nx &= \\dfrac{3}{8}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4x - \\dfrac{3}{8}\\) if \\(x=\\dfrac{3}{8}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 4\\left(\\dfrac{3}{8}\\right) - \\dfrac{3}{8} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{12}{8} - \\dfrac{3}{8} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{9}{8}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(3x\\) if \\(x=\\dfrac{3}{8}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 3\\left(\\dfrac{3}{8}\\right) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{9}{8}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(12x - 9 = 3x + 45 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n12x - 9 &= 3x + 45 \\\\\n12x - 3x &= 45 + 9 \\\\\n9x &= 54 \\\\\n\\dfrac{9x}{9} &= \\dfrac{54}{9} \\\\\nx &= 6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(12x - 9\\) if \\(x=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 12(6) - 9 \\\\\n&= 72 - 9 \\\\\n&= 63\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(3x + 45\\) if \\(x=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 3(6) + 45 \\\\\n&= 18 + 45 \\\\\n&= 63\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5n - 20 = -7n - 80 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5n - 20 &= -7n - 80 \\\\\n5n + 7n &= -80 + 20 \\\\\n12n &= -60 \\\\\n\\dfrac{12n}{12} &= \\dfrac{-60}{12} \\\\\nn &= -5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5n - 20\\) if \\(n=-5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 5(-5) - 20 \\\\\n&= -25 - 20 \\\\\n&= -45\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-7n - 80\\) if \\(n=-5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -7(-5) - 80 \\\\\n&= 35 - 80 \\\\\n&= -45\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4u + 16 = -19 - u \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4u + 16 &= -19 - u \\\\\n4u + u &= -19 - 16 \\\\\n5u &= -35 \\\\\n\\dfrac{5u}{5} &= \\dfrac{-35}{5} \\\\\nu &= -7\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4u + 16\\) if \\(u=-7\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 4(-7) + 16 \\\\\n&= -28 + 16 \\\\\n&= -12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-19 - u\\) if \\(u=-7\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -19 - (-7) \\\\\n&= -19 + 7 \\\\\n&= -12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{8}c - 4 = \\dfrac{3}{8}c + 4 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{5}{8}c - 4 &= \\dfrac{3}{8}c + 4 \\\\\n8 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{5}{8}c - 4\\right) &= 8 \\times \\left( \\dfrac{3}{8}c + 4 \\right) \\\\\n8 \\times \\dfrac{5}{8}c - 8 \\times 4 &= 8 \\times \\dfrac{3}{8}c + 8 \\times 4 \\\\\n5c - 32 &= 3c + 32 \\\\\n5c - 3c &= 32 + 32 \\\\\n2c &= 64 \\\\\n\\dfrac{2c}{2} &= \\dfrac{64}{2} \\\\\nc &= 32\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{5}{8}c - 4\\) if \\(c=32\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{5}{8}(32) - 4 \\\\\n&= 20 - 4 \\\\\n&= 16\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{3}{8}c + 4\\) if \\(c=32\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{3}{8}(32) + 4  \\\\\n&= 12 + 4 \\\\\n&= 16\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6(x + 6) = 24 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6(x + 6) &= 24 \\\\\n6x + 36 &= 24 \\\\\n6x &= 24 - 36 \\\\\n6x &= -12 \\\\\n\\dfrac{6x}{6} &= \\dfrac{-12}{6} \\\\\nx &= -2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 24</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(6(x+6)\\) if \\(x=-2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 6(-2 + 6) \\\\\n&= 6(4) \\\\\n&= 24\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9(2p - 5) = 72 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n9(2p - 5) &= 72 \\\\\n18p - 45 &= 72 \\\\\n18p &= 72 + 45 \\\\\n18p &= 117 \\\\\n\\dfrac{18p}{18} &= \\dfrac{117}{18} \\\\\np &= 6.5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 72</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(9(2p-5)\\) if \\(p=6.5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 9(2(6.5) - 5) \\\\\n&= 9(13 - 5) \\\\\n&= 9(8) \\\\\n&= 72\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-(s + 4) = 18 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-(s + 4) &= 18 \\\\\n-s - 4 &= 18 \\\\\n-s &= 18 + 4 \\\\\n-s &= 22 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-s}{-1} &= \\dfrac{22}{-1} \\\\\ns &= -22\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 18</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-(s+4)\\) if \\(s=-1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -(-22 + 4) \\\\\n&= -(-18) \\\\\n&= 18 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 + 3(n - 9) = 17 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8 + 3(n - 9) &= 17 \\\\\n8 + 3n - 27 &= 17 \\\\\n3n &= 17 + 27 - 8 \\\\\n3n &= 36 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3n}{3} &= \\dfrac{36}{3} \\\\\nn &= 12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 17</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(8 + 3(n - 9)\\) if \\(n=12\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 8 + 3(12 - 9) \\\\\n&= 8 + 3(3) \\\\\n&= 8 + 9 \\\\\n&= 17\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(23 - 3(y - 7) = 8 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n23 - 3(y - 7) &= 8 \\\\\n23 - 3y + 21 &= 8 \\\\\n-3y &= 8 - 21 - 23 \\\\\n-3y &= -36 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-3y}{-3} &= \\dfrac{-36}{-3} \\\\\ny &= 12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 8</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(23 - 3(y - 7)\\) if \\(y=12\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 23 - 3(12 - 7) \\\\\n&= 23 - 3(5) \\\\\n&= 23 - 15 \\\\\n&= 8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3}(6m + 21) = m - 7 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{3}(6m + 21) &= m - 7 \\\\\n3 \\times \\dfrac{1}{3}(6m + 21) &= 3 \\times (m - 7) \\\\\n6m + 21 &= 3m - 21 \\\\\n6m - 3m &= -21 - 21 \\\\\n3m &= -42 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3m}{3} &= \\dfrac{-42}{3} \\\\\nm &= -14\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{1}{3}(6m + 21)\\) if \\(m=-14\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{1}{3}(6(-14) + 21) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{1}{3}(-84 + 21) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{1}{3}(-63) \\\\\n&= -21\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Evaluate \\(m - 7\\) if \\(m=-14\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -14 - 7 \\\\\n&= -21\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8(r - 2) = 6(r + 10) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8(r - 2) &= 6(r + 10) \\\\\n8r - 16 &= 6r + 60 \\\\\n8r - 6r &= 60 + 16 \\\\\n2r = 76 \\\\\n\\dfrac{2r}{2} &= \\dfrac{76}{2} \\\\\nr &= 38\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(8(r - 2)\\) if \\(r=38\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 8(38 - 2) \\\\\n&= 8(36) \\\\\n&= 288\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Evaluate \\(6(r + 10)\\) if \\(r=38\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 6(38 + 10) \\\\\n&= 6(48) \\\\\n&= 288\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 + 7(2 - 5x) = 2(9x + 1) - (13x - 57) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5 + 7(2 - 5x) &= 2(9x + 1) - (13x - 57) \\\\\n5 + 14 - 35x &= 18x + 2 - 13x + 57 \\\\\n-35x - 18x + 13x &= 57 + 2 - 5 - 14 \\\\\n-40x = 40 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-40x}{-40} &= \\dfrac{40}{-40} \\\\\nx &= -1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5 + 7(2 - 5x)\\) if \\(x=-1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 5 + 7(2 - 5(-1)) \\\\\n&= 5 + 7(2 + 5) \\\\\n&= 5 + 7(7) \\\\\n&= 5 + 49 \\\\\n&= 54\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(9x + 1) - (13x - 57)\\) if \\(x=-1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 2(9(-1) + 1) - (13(-1) - 57) \\\\\n&= 2(-9 + 1) - (-13 - 57) \\\\\n&= 2(-8) - (-70) \\\\\n&= -16 + 70 \\\\\n&= 54\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4(3.5y + 0.25) = 365 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4(3.5y + 0.25) &= 365 \\\\\n14y + 1 &= 365 \\\\\n14y &= 365 - 1 \\\\\n14y = 364 \\\\\n\\dfrac{14y}{14} &= \\dfrac{364}{14} \\\\\ny &= 26\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 365</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4(3.5y + 0.25)\\) if \\(y=26\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 4(3.5(26) + 0.25) \\\\\n&= 4(91 + 0.25) \\\\\n&= 4(91.25) \\\\\n&= 365\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.25(q - 8) = 0.1(q + 7) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.25(q - 8) &= 0.1(q + 7) \\\\\n0.25q - 2 &= 0.1q + 0.7 \\\\\n0.25q - 0.1q &= 0.7 + 2 \\\\\n0.15q = 2.7 \\\\\n\\dfrac{0.15q}{0.15} &= \\dfrac{2.7}{0.15} \\\\\nq &= 18\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.25(q - 8)\\) if \\(q=18\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 0.25(18 - 8) \\\\\n&= 0.25(10) \\\\\n&=2.5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.1(q + 7)\\) if \\(q=18\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 0.1(18 + 7) \\\\\n&= 0.1(25) \\\\\n&=2.5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{5}n - \\dfrac{1}{10} = \\dfrac{7}{10} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{2}{5}n - \\dfrac{1}{10} &= \\dfrac{7}{10} \\\\\n10 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{2}{5}n - \\dfrac{1}{10}\\right) &= 10 \\times \\dfrac{7}{10} \\\\\n10 \\times \\dfrac{2}{5}n - 10 \\times \\dfrac{1}{10} &= 7 \\\\\n2(2n) - 1 &= 7 \\\\\n4n &= 7 + 1 \\\\\n4n &= 8 \\\\\n\\dfrac{4n}{4} &= \\dfrac{8}{4} \\\\\nn &= 2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = \\(\\dfrac{7}{10}\\)</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{2}{5}n - \\dfrac{1}{10}\\) if \\(n=2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{2}{5}(2) - \\dfrac{1}{10} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{4}{5} - \\dfrac{1}{10} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{7}{10}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3}x + \\dfrac{1}{5}x = 8 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{3}x + \\dfrac{1}{5}x &= 8 \\\\\n15 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{1}{3}x + \\dfrac{1}{5}x\\right) &= 15 \\times 8 \\\\\n15 \\times \\dfrac{1}{3}x + 15 \\times \\dfrac{1}{5}x &= 120 \\\\\n5x + 3x &= 120 \\\\\n8x &= 120 \\\\\n\\dfrac{8x}{8} &= \\dfrac{120}{8} \\\\\nx &= 15\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 8</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{1}{3}x + \\dfrac{1}{5}x\\) if \\(x=15\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{1}{3}(15) + \\dfrac{1}{5}(15) \\\\\n&= 5 + 3 \\\\\n&= 8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{4}a - \\dfrac{1}{3} = \\dfrac{1}{2}a + \\dfrac{5}{6} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{3}{4}a - \\dfrac{1}{3} &= \\dfrac{1}{2}a + \\dfrac{5}{6} \\\\\n12 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{3}{4}a - \\dfrac{1}{3}\\right) &= 12 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}a + \\dfrac{5}{6}\\right) \\\\\n12 \\times \\dfrac{3}{4}a - 12 \\times \\dfrac{1}{3} &= 12 \\times \\dfrac{1}{2}a + 12 \\times \\dfrac{5}{6} \\\\\n3 \\times 3a - 4 \\times 1 &= 6 \\times a + 2 \\times 5 \\\\\n9a - 4 &= 6a + 10 \\\\\n9a - 6a &= 10 + 4 \\\\\n3a &= 14 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3a}{3} &= \\dfrac{14}{3} \\\\\na &= \\dfrac{14}{3}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{3}{4}a - \\dfrac{1}{3}\\) if \\(a=\\dfrac{14}{3}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{3}{4}\\left(\\dfrac{14}{3}\\right) - \\dfrac{1}{3} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{7}{2} - \\dfrac{1}{3} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{19}{6}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{1}{2}a + \\dfrac{5}{6}\\) if \\(a=\\dfrac{14}{3}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{1}{2}\\left(\\dfrac{14}{3}\\right) + \\dfrac{5}{6} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{7}{3} + \\dfrac{5}{6} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{19}{6}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2}(k+3) = \\dfrac{1}{3}(k + 16) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{2}(k+3) &= \\dfrac{1}{3}(k + 16) \\\\\n6 \\times \\dfrac{1}{2}(k + 3) &= 6 \\times \\dfrac{1}{3}(k + 16) \\\\\n3(k + 3) &= 2(k + 16) \\\\\n3k + 9 &= 2k + 32 \\\\\n3k - 2k &= 32 - 9 \\\\\nk &= 23\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{1}{2}(k+3)\\) if \\(k=23\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{1}{2}(23+3) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{1}{2}(26) \\\\\n&= 13\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{1}{3}(k+16)\\) if \\(k=23\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{1}{3}(23+16) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{1}{3}(39) \\\\\n&= 13\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.8x - 0.3 = 0.7x + 0.2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.8x - 0.3 &= 0.7x + 0.2 \\\\\n0.8x - 0.7x &= 0.2 + 0.3 \\\\\n0.1x &= 0.5 \\\\\n\\dfrac{0.1x}{0.1} &= \\dfrac{0.5}{0.1} \\\\\nx &= 5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.8x - 0.3\\) if \\(x=-5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 0.8(5) - 0.3 \\\\\n&= 4 - 0.3 \\\\\n&= 3.7\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.7x + 0.2\\) if \\(x=5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 0.7(5) + 0.2 \\\\\n&= 3.5 + 0.2 \\\\\n&= 3.7\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.36a + 2.55 = 0.41a + 6.8 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.36a + 2.55 &= 0.41a + 6.8 \\\\\n0.36a - 0.41a &= 6.8 - 2.55 \\\\\n-0.05a &= 4.25 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-0.05a}{-0.05} &= \\dfrac{4.25}{-0.05} \\\\\na &= -85\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.36a + 2.55\\) if \\(a=-85\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 0.36(-85) + 2.55 \\\\\n&= -30.6 + 2.55 \\\\\n&= -28.05\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.41a + 6.8\\) if \\(a=-85\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 0.41(-85) + 6.8 \\\\\n&= -34.85 + 6.8 \\\\\n&= -28.05\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.6p - 1.9 = 0.78p + 1.7 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.6p - 1.9 &= 0.78p + 1.7 \\\\\n0.6p - 0.78p &= 1.7 + 1.9 \\\\\n-0.18p &= 3.6 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-0.18p}{-0.18} &= \\dfrac{3.6}{-0.18} \\\\\np &= -20\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.6p - 1.9\\) if \\(p=-20\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 0.6(-20) - 1.9 \\\\\n&= -12 - 1.9 \\\\\n&= -13.9\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.78p + 1.7\\) if \\(p=-20\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 0.78(-20) + 1.7 \\\\\n&= -15.6 + 1.7 \\\\\n&= -13.9\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.10d + 0.05(d - 4) = 2.05 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.10d + 0.05(d - 4) &= 2.05 \\\\\n0.10d + 0.05d - 0.2 &= 2.05 \\\\\n0.15d &= 2.05 + 0.2 \\\\\n0.15d &= 2.25 \\\\\n\\dfrac{0.15d}{0.15} &= \\dfrac{2.25}{0.15} \\\\\nd &= 15\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 2.05</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.10d + 0.05(d - 4)\\) if \\(d=15\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 0.10(15) + 0.05(15 - 4) \\\\\n&= 1.5 + 0.05(11) \\\\\n&= 1.5 + 0.55 \\\\\n&= 2.05 \n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(n - 18 = 31 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nn - 18 &= 31 \\\\\nn &= 31 + 18 \\\\\nn &= 49\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 31</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(n - 18\\) if \\(n=49\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 49 - 18 \\\\\n&= 31\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9c = 144 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n9c &= 144 \\\\\n\\dfrac{9c}{9} &= \\dfrac{144}{9} \\\\\nc &= 16\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 144</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(9c\\) if \\(c=16\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 9(16) \\\\\n&= 144\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4y - 8 = 16 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4y - 8 &= 16 \\\\\n4y &= 16 + 8 \\\\\n4y &= 24 \\\\\n\\dfrac{4y}{4} &= \\dfrac{24}{4} \\\\\ny &= 6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 16</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4y - 8\\) if \\(y=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 4(6) - 8 \\\\\n&= 24 - 8 \\\\\n&= 16\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-8x - 15 + 9x - 1 = -21 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-8x - 15 + 9x - 1 &= -21 \\\\\n-8x + 9x &= -21 + 15 + 1 \\\\\nx &= -5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -21</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-8x - 15 + 9x - 1\\) if \\(x=-5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -8(-5) - 15 + 9(-5) - 1 \\\\\n&= 40 - 15- 45 - 1 \\\\\n&= -21\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-15a = 120 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-15a &= 120 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-15a}{-15} &= \\dfrac{120}{-15} \\\\\na &= -8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 120</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-15a\\) if \\(a=-8\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -15(-8) \\\\\n&= 120\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{3}x = 6 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{2}{3}x &= 6 \\\\\n3 \\times \\dfrac{2}{3}x &= 3 \\times 6 \\\\\n2x &= 18 \\\\\n\\dfrac{2x}{2} &= \\dfrac{18}{2} \\\\\nx &= 9\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 6</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{2}{3}x\\) if \\(x=9\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{2}{3}(9) \\\\\n&= 6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(x + 3.8 = 8.2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nx + 3.8 &= 8.2 \\\\\nx &= 8.2 - 3.8 \\\\\nx &= 4.4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 8.2</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(x + 3.8\\) if \\(x=4.4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 4.4 + 3.8 \\\\\n&= 8.2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(10y = -5y + 60 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10y &= -5y + 60 \\\\\n10y + 5y &= 60 \\\\\n15y &= 60 \\\\\n\\dfrac{15y}{15} &= \\dfrac{60}{15} \\\\\ny &= 4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(10y\\) if \\(y=4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 10(4) \\\\\n&= 40\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-5y + 60\\) if \\(y=4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -5(4) + 60 \\\\\n&= -20 + 60 \\\\\n&= 40\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8n + 2 = 6n + 12 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8n + 2 &= 6n + 12 \\\\\n8n - 6n &= 12 -2 \\\\\n2n &= 10 \\\\\n\\dfrac{2n}{2} &= \\dfrac{10}{2} \\\\\nn &= 5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(8n + 2\\) if \\(n=5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 8(5) + 2 \\\\\n&= 40 + 2 \\\\\n&= 42\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(6n + 12\\) if \\(n=5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 6(5) + 12 \\\\\n&= 30 + 12 \\\\\n&= 42\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9m - 2 - 4m + m = 42 - 8 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n9m - 2 - 4m + m &= 42 - 8 \\\\\n9m - 4m + m &= 42 -8+2 \\\\\n6m &= 36 \\\\\n\\dfrac{6m}{6} &= \\dfrac{36}{6} \\\\\nm &= 6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 34</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(9m - 2 - 4m + m\\) if \\(m=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 9(6) - 2 - 4(6) + 6 \\\\\n&= 54 - 2 - 24 + 6 \\\\\n&= 34\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-5(2x + 1) = 45 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-5(2x + 1) &= 45 \\\\\n-10x - 5 &= 45 \\\\\n-10x &= 45 + 5 \\\\\n-10x &= 50 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-10x}{-10} &= \\dfrac{50}{-10} \\\\\nx &= -5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 45</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-5(2x + 1)\\) if \\(x=-5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -5(2(-5) + 1) \\\\\n&= -5(-10 + 1) \\\\\n&= -5(-9) \\\\\n&= 45\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-(d + 9) = 23 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-(d + 9) &= 23 \\\\\n-d - 9 &= 23 \\\\\n-d &= 23 + 9 \\\\\n-d &= 32 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-d}{-1} &= \\dfrac{32}{-1} \\\\\nd &= -32\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 23</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-(d + 9)\\) if \\(d=-32\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= -(-32 + 9) \\\\\n&= -(-23) \\\\\n&= 23\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2(6x+ 5) - 8 = -22 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(6x+ 5) - 8 &= -22 \\\\\n12x + 10 - 8 &= -22 \\\\\n12x &= -22 + 8 - 10 \\\\\n12x &= -24 \\\\\n\\dfrac{12x}{12} &= \\dfrac{-24}{12} \\\\\nx &= -2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -22</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(6x+ 5) - 8\\) if \\(x=-2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 2(6(-2) + 5) - 8 \\\\\n&= 2(-12 + 5) - 8 \\\\\n&= 2(-7) - 8 \\\\\n&= -14 - 8 \\\\\n&= -22\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8(3a + 5) - 7(4a - 3) = 20 - 3a \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8(3a + 5) - 7(4a - 3) &= 20 - 3a \\\\\n24a + 40 - 28a + 21 &= 20 - 3a \\\\\n24a - 28a + 3a &= 20 - 21 - 40 \\\\\n-a &= -41 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-a}{-1} &= \\dfrac{-41}{-1} \\\\\na &= 41\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(8(3a + 5) - 7(4a - 3)\\) if \\(a=41\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 8(3(41) + 5) - 7(4(41) - 3) \\\\\n&= 8(123 + 5) -7(164 - 3) \\\\\n&= 8(128) - 7(161) \\\\\n&= -1024 - 1127 \\\\\n&= -103\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(20 -3a\\) if \\(a=41\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 20 - 3(41) \\\\\n&= 20 - 123 \\\\\n&= -103\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{4}p + \\dfrac{1}{3} = \\dfrac{1}{2} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{4}p + \\dfrac{1}{3} &= \\dfrac{1}{2} \\\\\n12 \\times \\left(\\dfrac{1}{4}p + \\dfrac{1}{3}\\right) &=12 \\times \\dfrac{1}{2}\\\\\n12 \\times \\dfrac{1}{4}p + 12 \\times \\dfrac{1}{3} &= 6 \\\\\n3p + 4 &= 6 \\\\\n3p &= 6 - 4 \\\\\n3p &= 2 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3p}{3} &= \\dfrac{2}{3} \\\\\np &= \\dfrac{2}{3}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = \\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{1}{4}p + \\dfrac{1}{3}\\) if \\(p=\\dfrac{2}{3}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= \\dfrac{1}{4}\\left(\\dfrac{2}{3}\\right) + \\dfrac{1}{3} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{1}{6} + \\dfrac{1}{3} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{1}{2}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.1d + 0.25(d + 8) = 4.1 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.1d + 0.25(d + 8) &= 4.1 \\\\\n0.1d + 0.25d + 2 &= 4.1 \\\\\n0.1d + 0.25d &= 4.1 - 2 \\\\\n0.35d &= 2.1 \\\\\n\\dfrac{0.35d}{0.35} &= \\dfrac{2.1}{0.35} \\\\\nd &= 6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 4.1</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.1d + 0.25(d + 8)\\) if \\(d=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&= 0.1(6) + 0.25(6 + 8) \\\\\n&= 0.6 + 0.25(14) \\\\\n&= 0.6 + 3.5 \\\\\n&= 4.1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    }
  ]
}
